Dorothy Norman Papers
Dorothy Norman Papers
- Published material (1968 Accession)
  - Pamphlets
    - "Towards a Fuller Life in Bombay Province,", October, 1946-March, 1948 (Box 59)
    - "Trade and Aid," B.P. Lamb, 1953 (Box 59)
    - "The Training Ship Dufferin,", May 1949 (Box 59)
    - "The Twelve Months of War in Kashmir,", October 22, 1947 (Box 59)
    - "Twentieth Century India", 1944 (Box 59)
    - "Understanding Asia,", June 1951 (Box 59)
    - UNESCO, 1948 (Box 59)
    - "United Provinces Social Services Training Scheme,", March 28, 1948 (Box 59)
    - "UP's Prosperity Plan", undated (Box 59)
    - "Views of Maganradi", undated (Box 59)
    - "We Put Freedom First,", June 25, 1950 (Box 59)
    - "What They Think of Me," K.N. Katju, July 24, 1949 (Box 59)
    - "Women's Welfare Work", 1948 (Box 59)
    - "The Work of the Asia Foundation," Robert Blum, March 1956 (Box 59)
    - "The Exodus of Christians from Pakistan,", 1964 (Box 59)
    - "World Problems and Our Peaceful Policy," Dr. Najib Ullah, February 2, 1952 (Box 59)
  - Periodicals
    - Asia, 1939 (Box 59)
    - Asiatic Digest, 1950 (Box 59)
    - The Adyar Library Bulletin, 1954 (Box 59)
    - Chetanai, 1959 (Box 59)
    - China Report, 1966 (Box 59)
    - Common Sense, 1944 (Box 59)
    - Cultural News, 1963 (Box 59)
    - Far Eastern Survey, 1945; 1955; 2 items (Box 59)
    - Field Reporter, 1952; 2 items (Box 59)
    - Gandhi Marq, 1965 (Box 59)
    - The Hindu Weekly Review, 1965-1967; 43 items (Box 59)
    - Indian and Foreign Review, 1967 complete, 1964-1968; 24 items (Box 60)
    - Indonesia, 1957; 1958 (Box 60)
    - Jadapour Journal of Comparative Literature, 1964 (Box 60)
    - Kalakshatra, 1961; 1962; 2 items (Box 60)
    - Nataya, 1959-1960; 2 items (Box 60)
    - New History, 1944 (Box 60)
    - Quest, 1955-1967; 18 items (Box 60)
    - Rehabilitation Review, 1949 (Box 60)
    - Round Table, 1944 (Box 60)
    - Seminar, 1962-1966; 25 items (Box 60)
    - The Survey, 1950 (Box 60)
    - U.P. Information, 1947; 2 items (Box 60)
    - Voice of India, 1946 (Box 60)
    - Weekend Review, 1966-1967; 19 items (Box 60)
    - Weekly India News, 1963-1968 (Box 61)
    - Yojana, 1966 (Box 61)
  - Reports
    - Adivasi Seva Mandal, Sixth Annual Report, 1948 (Box 61)
    - The All-India Village Industries Association, 1946 (Box 61)
    - The All-India Women's Conference, 1949 (Box 61)
    - The All-India Women's Conference, 1950 (Box 61)
    - Appendix to Demands for Grants, 1951 (Box 61)
    - Bharay Sevak Samaj, 1952 (Box 61)
    - The Bombay Tenancy and Agricultural Lands Act, 1948 (Box 61)
    - A Brief Account of the Various Activities by the Textile Labour Association Ahmedabad (Box 61)
    - Budget of the Central Government of Pakistan, 1949 (Box 61)
    - Budget of the Central Government of Pakistan, 1950 (Box 61)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1958 (Box 61)
    - The Case against Increased Import Barriers on Lead and Zinc, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Central Banking in India, 1948 (Box 61)
    - Central Budget for 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - Central Budget for 1949-1950 (Box 61)
    - Council of Scientific and Industrial Research (India), 1949 (Box 61)
    - A Decade of Labour Legislation in India, 1937-1948 (Box 61)
    - Dharave, An Economic and Social Survey of a Village in the Suburbs of Bombay (Box 61)
    - Employees State Insurance Act, 1948 (Box 61)
    - Government of Pakistan Budget, 1950-1951 (Box 61)
    - Hind Mazdoor Sabha, Report of the Calcutta Conference, 1948 (Box 61)
    - India Record, 1950 (Box 61)
    - India United Mills, Labour Welfare Activities, 1944-1948 (Box 61)
    - Indian Hospitality Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - Indian National Congress, 56th session, 1950 (Box 61)
    - Indian National Congress, 57th session, 1951 (Box 61)
    - Industrial Finance Corporation of India, 1949 (Box 61)
    - Information on Scholarships (Box 61)
    - Let Figures Tell, 1949 (Box 61)
    - Madras Civil Liberties Union, 1948 (Box 61)
    - Memorandum, Idara Talum-O-Tara QQI, Institute of Adult and Social Education (Box 61)
    - Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - Mutual Security Act of 1952 Conference Report (Box 61)
    - Mutual Security Program for Fiscal Year, 1953 (Box 61)
    - Mutual Security Program for Fiscal Year, 1954 (Box 61)
    - The Mutual Security Program, Second Report for Congress, 1952 (Box 61)
    - The Mutual Security Program, Third Report to Congress, 1952 (Box 61)
    - Progress of Co-operatives in the United Provinces, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - The Ramakrishna Mission Institute of Culture, 1948 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Health Survey and Development Committee, 1945 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Islamia Hospital, 1945-1946 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Islamia Hospital, 1946-1947 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Islamia Hospital, 1947-1948 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Islamia Hospital, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - Report on Kalakshetra, 1936-1961 (Box 61)
    - Report on the Working of the Forest Labourers' Co-operative Society, 1947-1948 (Box 61)
    - Report of the Working of the Forest Labourers' Co-operative Society, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - A Report to You (Box 61)
    - Resolution and Statement, 1948 (Box 61)
    - A Retrospect, Administration of United Provinces, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
    - Seven Years of Work, 8th Annual Report, 1938-1946 (Box 61)
    - The Sinners Sind, 1946 (Box 61)
    - Some Typical Non-Credit Societies in India, 1933 (Box 61)
    - State vs. Liberty, 1949 (Box 61)
    - Stockpile Report to the Congress, 1953 (Box 61)
    - Supplement to Demands for Grants, 1950-1951 (Box 61)
    - U.N. Commission for India and Pakistan, 1948 (Box 61)
    - Working of the Workman's Compensation Act, 1923; 1947 (Box 61)